Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG 37.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Director's Files
  - Subseries C: Institutions
    - Harvard Educational Review, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Harvard University, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Harvard University Press, 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273279
    - Harvard Society of Fellows, 1978-1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Architecture and Urban Studies - MacNair, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - NYU Institute of Fine Arts, 1971-1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Institute for Philosophy of Science, Psychotherapy and Ethics, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Institute for Policy Studies, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Creative Management, 1976-1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - International Federation of Chemical Worker's Unions, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - International Society for the Comparative Study of Civilizations, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - International Society of Political Psychology, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Jovanovich Harcourt, Brace/William, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Kenyon Review, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - London Review of Books, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - London School of Economics, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Lyon Université, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1977-1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Miami University, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Minuit Revue Périodique, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Le Monde, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - The Nation, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - The National Book Critics Circle, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978-1984 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - National Gay Task Force, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - National Science Foundation, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - National Science Foundation, 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - National Science Foundation, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273287
    - New York Review of Books, 1977-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - New York Times, 1978-1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - The New Yorker, 1978-1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Newsweek, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Partisan Review, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - PEN, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Oxford University Press, 1979-1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Pantheon Books, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Princeton University, 1982-1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Review of Existentialist Psychology & Psychiatry, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - David Riesman Festschrift, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - The Rockefeller University, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Deborah Rogers Ltd., 1976-1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Royal Institute of British Architects, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Moshe Safdie & Associates, 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Secker & Warburg, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Signs Journal of Women in Culture & Society, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Kalman Silvert Festschrift, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Simon & Schuster, Inc., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Société Européenne de Culture, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Society of Fellows, New York University, 1978-1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Social and Public Art Resource Center SPARC, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Southwestern at Memphis, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273295
    - Theory & Society, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Times Literary Supplement, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The Tocqueville Association, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Transaction Publishers, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Trinity College, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Tuttle-Mori Agency, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Vanity Fair, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Viking Press, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Vogue Magazine, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Voices, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Yale Law School, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D: Subject Files
    - Before Stonewall, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Bellagio Conference on Humanities and Social Thought, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Bucharest Conference, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Norman Cantor: "The Dream Deferred", 1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Chrysler Forum, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Cornell University - Society for the Humanities, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - The Council on Foundations Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Conference of Europeanists, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Douglas/Wollaeger - Towards a Typology of the Viewing Public, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Exxon, 1977-1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Fall of Public Man, 1974-1983 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Family Educational Rights & Privacy Act of, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Freud Lecture, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Goldberger-Freud Project, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Graz Literary Festival Frankfurt/London, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - The Human Figure on the Stage & in the Street Exhibit, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273303
    - International Sociology Meeting, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - International Distributive Justice Ronald Findlay, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Jerusalem, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Frances Myrna Kamm "Equal Concern and Respect for Unequal Numbers", 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Ambassador Theater, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Barrymore Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Belasco Theater Interior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Belasco Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Biltmore Theater Interior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Booth Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Broadhurst Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Brooks Atkinson Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Cort Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Embassy I Theater, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Eugene O'Neill Theater, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Forty-Sixth Street Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Gerard Hotel Exterior, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Golden Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Henry Miller Theater, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Hudson Theater, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Imperial Theater, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Landmarks Preservation - The Lamb's Club, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Landmarks Preservation - The Little Theater, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Longacre Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Lunt-Fontaine, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Lyceum Theater, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Majestic Theater, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273311
    - Landmarks Preservation - Music Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Landmarks Preservation - New Amsterdam Theater, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Plymouth Theatre, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Royale Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Landmarks Preservation - St. James Theater, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Palace Theater, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Schubert Theater Exterior, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Town Hall, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Winter Garden Theater, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - University of Michigan "Narcissism in Modern Society", 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - NY Office of Midtown Enforcement Annual Report, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - NY Office of Midtown Enforcement Annual Report, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - NYC Crime Statistics - Midtown Precincts, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Music and Sociology (ASA/Aspen), 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - National Endowment for the Arts Proposal, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - National Town Meeting, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - New Republic Letters re: Sontag, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - The New Right and Current Affairs, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - New School for Social Research Graduate Faculty, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Participation & Disorder in Urban Form Conference, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - PEN Freedom to Write, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - PEN Human Rights, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - PEN Lease, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - PEN Nominations for Officers and Board, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Penguin Books, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273329
    - Press Clippings, 1979-1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Public Sexuality and Hiding Behavior D.A. Karp, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Publishers - France, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Publishers - Italian, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Publishers - German, 1977-1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Recontres Internationales de Geneve, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Random House, 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Red Markings, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Claude Roquin Translation Paperwork, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Moshe Safdie Exhibition Catalog, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Moshe Safdie Lecture & Exhibit Correspondence, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Fellows' Scrapbook, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - George Segal Liberation Sculpture, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Richard Sennett Essays and Transcripts, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273337
    - Richard Sennett Essays and Transcripts, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Robert R. Holt: Sennett Proposal for "Personality, Moral Development, and the Humanities", 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Union Visit, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - NYU Office of Sponsored Programs, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The Theory of the State, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Virgil Thomson "Music Does Not Flow", undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - De Tocqueville Conference, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Triumph or Downfall of Civil Society Alain Touraine, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - UNESCO American Embassy Residence, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Judith R. Walkowitz "Jack the Ripper & the Myth of Male Violence", 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Wellfleet Meetings, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Work in America: A Decade Later (Ford Foundation), 1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Series II: Seminars, Lectures and Events
  - Acting in Everyday Life and Everyday Life in Acting Victor Turner, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - The Actor As a Celebrity Richard Gilman, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Quentin Anderson Symposium, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Anthropological Aspects of Television, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Architecture in New York, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Architecture of Confinement (Tom Bender), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273345
  - Arendt Conference, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Arendt Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Auden Festival, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Auden Festival Accounts, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Auden Festival Invitations, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Auden Festival Publicity, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Authority Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Roland Barthes Conference, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Charles A. Beard Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Jessica Benjamin Seminar, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273352
  - Ronald Blythe Lecture, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Biography Seminar, 1981-1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Biography Seminar Budget, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Biography Seminar - Meeting Summaries, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Biography Seminar Readings, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Biography Seminar Readings, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Book Parties (Receptions), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Jorge Luis Borges Seminar, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Borges Lecture, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Borges Events RSVPs, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Breyten Breytenbach, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Censorship Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Censorship Conference Transcript, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273360
  - Commercial Culture Seminar, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Communism, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Communism and the Intellectual Seminar, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - A Program in Comparative Cultural Studies, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Constructing America, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Constructing America Readings, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Culture and the Actor, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Culture and the Actor - Roger Shattuck, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Culture and Economics, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Culture of Cities, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Culture of Cities, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273378
  - Culture of Cities, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Culture of Cities - General, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Natalie Zemon Davis Lecture, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Daniel Defert Symposium, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Jacques Derrida "The Law of Genre", 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - An Evening of Brahms, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Exiled Writers Program, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fellows Lunches, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fellows Lunches - Speakers, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fellows Meetings, 1977-1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273386
  - Fiscal Crisis in New York City, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Foucault Conference, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Foucault/Habermas, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Freedom and Censorship in the Schools, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Friday Lunch Seminars, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Future of the Intellectual in New York, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Gallatin Lectures: Edmund Leach, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Gallatin Lectures: Edward Stankiewicz, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Galway Kinnell Readings, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Gemant Lecture on Science and the Humanities, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Geopolitics of Information (Anthony Smith), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Anthony Giddens: From Marx to Nietzsche?, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Phillip Glass, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Phillip Glass Gallatin Lecture Transcript, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Nadine Gordimer Transcript, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Jurgen Habermas: Modernity vs Post-Modernity Transcripts, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Marilyn Hacker, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Peter Hanak Lecture, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Homosexuality Seminar, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273394
  - Humanists in Museums Conference, 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Humanists in Museums - Financial, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Inventing Times Square - Billboards and Signs, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Interpretation Seminar, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Inventing Times Square, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Inventing Times Square - Peter Buckley, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Inventing Times Square - Computer Notes, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Inventing Times Square - Lewis Erenberg, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Inventing Times Square - Richard Fox, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Inventing Times Square - Timothy Gilfoyle, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Inventing Times Square - David C. Hammack, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Inventing Times Square - Ada Louise Huxtable, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Inventing Times Square - J.B Jackson, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Inventing Times Square - Dana C. Kinstler Correpsondence, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Inventing Times Square - Bill Leach, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Inventing Times Square - Larry May, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Inventing Times Square - Brooks McNamara, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Inventing Times Square - Minda Novek Memos, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273402
  - Inventing Times Square - Michael Schudson, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Inventing Times Square - Laurence Senelick, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Inventing Times Square - Kate Simon, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Inventing Times Square - Participants' Letters of Response, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Inventing Times Square - Research Sources, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Inventing Times Square - Bill Taylor, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Inventing Times Square - Tobier Papers, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Inventing Times Square - Joseph Urban, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Roman Jakobson, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - James Lectures Posters, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - James Lectures, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - James Lectures, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - James Lectures Invitations, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - James Lectures, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - James Lectures, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - James Lecture - Borges, Valenzuela, Coleman Transcript, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - James Lecture - Italo Calvino "The Written and Unwritten Word", Spring, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - James Lecture - Sir Stuart Hampshire "History and Conflict", 1983 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - James Lecture - Francis Haskell "Modern Art and its Enemies in the 19th Century", undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273410
  - James Lecture - Frances Haskell: Modern Art and Its Enemies in the 19th Century: Transcript, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - James Lecture - Czeslaw Milosz "Conversation on Writing and Politics", 1981 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - James Lecture - Amartya Sen, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - James Lecture - William Weaver "Verdi's Taste", 1983 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Japan Conference Shitamachi Symposium, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Justin Kaplan - "The Art of Biography" Transcript, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Pavel Kohout "Conversation on Writing and Politics", 1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Leszek Kolakowski - Lecture, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - George Konrad Reception, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Lacan Conference Programs, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Law & Philosophy Seminar, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Law and Philosophy Seminar, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Law of the Sea Conference, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Law of the Sea Conference, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273428
  - Literature and Censorship, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Marxism & Capitalism, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Masculinity Seminar, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Matrix - Mailing List, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Yehudi Menuhin - Lecture, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Modernisms, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Alberto Moravia - "Writing and Politics", 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Motherhood and Feminism Seminar, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Mothers and the Avant-Garde, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Narrative Seminar, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Narrative Seminar, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Narrative Seminar - Budget, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - New American Music Reception, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - The New Right Seminar - Correspondence, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - The New Right Seminar - Readings, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273436
  - The New Right Seminar - Readings, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The New Right Seminar - Readings, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - NYIH Open House Party - October, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Personal Elements in Professional Authority Seminar, Barbara Ehrenreich, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Poet's House Events, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Richard Poirier "People, Technology, Literature", undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Politics and Theory Proposed Seminar, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Pornography, Obscenity and Freedom, Bernard Williams, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Pre-Modernism, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - NYIH Programs Schedules, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Proof of Names Aryeh Neier, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273444
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Public Cultural Policy, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Steve Reich - Lecture Transcript 4/21/1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Religious Fundamentalism Conference, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Oliver Sacks - Lecture Transcript, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Moshe Safdie Lecture and Exhibit - Related Materials, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Saskia Sassen-Koob - New York City Seminar, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273451
  - Science and the Humanities - Discussion Transcript, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Seminars, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Seminars, 1986-1991 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Seminar Fees, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Seminars - General Information, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Richard Sennett - "The Frog Who Dared to Croak" Reception, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273469
  - Sexuality and Solitude Michel Foucault and Richard Sennett Seminar, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Sexuality and Solitude Michel Foucault and Richard Sennett Seminar Readings, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Sexuality and Solitude Michel Foucault and Richard Sennett Transcripts, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - The Shadow, The Mirror, & the Double Ewa Kuryluk, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Stephen Spender Conversation Transcript, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Stephen Spender "The Poet as 'I' in his Poem", undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Taste Seminar - David Rieff & Edmund White, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Television Styles: Towards a Typology of the Viewing Public, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Mary Douglas, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Television & Popular Culture - Tod Gitlin, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Textuality - Perry Meisel, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)